[Music]
welcome to another video and this one is
for all you chocoholics out there
specifically cadburysaholics yes it's
the ultimate cadburys
ice cream now to make your custard ice
cream base
combine into a pan 500 mil of
milk and 300 grams of sugar
and gently heat on the hob until all the
sugar has dissolved
and the milk is just starting to steam
now be careful not to overheat
and to boil the milk as you'll end up
with a burnt taste which
isn't very pleasant now add six egg
yolks into a separate bowl or jug
and gently temper the eggs by gradually
adding spoonfuls of the hot milk
and whisking vigorously continue to
slowly add around
five tablespoons of the milk and this
technique will gently bring the eggs up
to a temperature
and prevent the eggs from scrambling
when you add them back into the pan
but if in doubt just keep adding an
extra spoonful in
before pouring the eggs into the pan
keep the mixture moving by giving it a
good old stir
and now to make your ice cream chocolaty
add 120 grams
of cadburys dairy milk chocolate and two
heaped teaspoons of good quality cocoa
powder
to your pan keep it over your low heat
and just keep whiskey whiskey whiskey
melty melty melty
stir stir stir you get the pitcher just
keep mixing until it coats the back of
the spoon
and then pour it into a large jug
[Music]
here for your visual delight is all the
extra goodies we're going to be adding
to our ultimate cadburys ice cream
including a dark chocolate sauce and
cadbury's
fingers and a flake
next up pour in 600 ml of the double
cream
more whiskey whiskey whiskey to combine
and that is the epic chocolate ice cream
base
complete
pour this silky mixture into your ice
cream maker
and set it churning now we have
pre-chilled our
ice cream maker for around 20 minutes so
be sure to check if your machine
needs pre-chilling beforehand as some do
and some don't
while your ice cream is churning prep
your chosen cadbury add-ins
as we've said we've gone for fingers and
a flake but feel free to raid the
confectionery aisle at your local store
and choose your favorite cadburys chucky
treats
so go ahead and slice and dice these
into chunks
[Music]
and once your ice cream has reached your
desired soft serve consistency
ours takes around 20 minutes lovingly
throw in about half of your chocolate
chunks
into your ice cream mixture
[Music]
now we've been a little bit naughty here
and we've added in a boozy twist by
adding a drizzle
of mozart chocolate cream liqueur it
tastes absolutely amazing but of course
this is optional but give it another
quick go around
in the machine and make sure your
chocolate chunks are evenly distributed
throughout
and give it a compulsory taste test and
ooh and ah in the privacy of your
kitchen
over its epicness
[Music]
spoon half into your chosen container
and add the rest of your chocolate
[Music]
chunks
then the rest of your deliciously creamy
ice cream and finish
off with a generous squirt of dark
chocolate sauce
and just gently agitate it with a spoon
so you get a lovely
ribbons of sauce throughout your ice
cream
and that's it delicious creamy decadent
and a perfect way to satisfy any cadbury
aholic
thanks for joining us and if you enjoyed
this video please support our channel by
hitting the like and subscribe buttons
and we'll see you next time